{
    "trainings": [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "title": "Math training 1",
            "pack": "Addition",
            "problems": [
                {
                    "question": "93 + 5",
                    "answer": "98"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 8",
                    "answer": "32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "57 + 3",
                    "answer": "60"
                },
                {
                    "question": "39 + 3",
                    "answer": "42"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 + 4",
                    "answer": "19"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25 + 3",
                    "answer": "28"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 7",
                    "answer": "85"
                },
                {
                    "question": "38 + 9",
                    "answer": "47"
                },
                {
                    "question": "68 + 3",
                    "answer": "71"
                },
                {
                    "question": "73 + 4",
                    "answer": "77"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 9",
                    "answer": "72"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 8",
                    "answer": "43"
                },
                {
                    "question": "70 + 4",
                    "answer": "74"
                },
                {
                    "question": "94 + 9",
                    "answer": "103"
                },
                {
                    "question": "74 + 5",
                    "answer": "79"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 4",
                    "answer": "27"
                },
                {
                    "question": "76 + 6",
                    "answer": "82"
                },
                {
                    "question": "76 + 9",
                    "answer": "85"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 8",
                    "answer": "32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25 + 5",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 5",
                    "answer": "40"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 + 6",
                    "answer": "56"
                },
                {
                    "question": "80 + 4",
                    "answer": "84"
                },
                {
                    "question": "48 + 7",
                    "answer": "55"
                },
                {
                    "question": "30 + 4",
                    "answer": "34"
                },
                {
                    "question": "97 + 3",
                    "answer": "100"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12 + 9",
                    "answer": "21"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 8",
                    "answer": "31"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 3",
                    "answer": "26"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 3",
                    "answer": "81"
                },
                {
                    "question": "14 + 3",
                    "answer": "17"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 2",
                    "answer": "80"
                },
                {
                    "question": "47 + 5",
                    "answer": "52"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 + 8",
                    "answer": "23"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 3",
                    "answer": "81"
                },
                {
                    "question": "80 + 7",
                    "answer": "87"
                },
                {
                    "question": "44 + 3",
                    "answer": "47"
                },
                {
                    "question": "30 + 2",
                    "answer": "32"
                },
                {
                    "question": "16 + 2",
                    "answer": "18"
                },
                {
                    "question": "82 + 9",
                    "answer": "91"
                },
                {
                    "question": "36 + 8",
                    "answer": "44"
                },
                {
                    "question": "59 + 2",
                    "answer": "61"
                },
                {
                    "question": "74 + 8",
                    "answer": "82"
                },
                {
                    "question": "81 + 4",
                    "answer": "85"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 8",
                    "answer": "71"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 7",
                    "answer": "70"
                },
                {
                    "question": "96 + 9",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "93 + 5",
                    "answer": "98"
                },
                {
                    "question": "98 + 6",
                    "answer": "104"
                },
                {
                    "question": "68 + 3",
                    "answer": "71"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12 + 3",
                    "answer": "15"
                },
                {
                    "question": "72 + 8",
                    "answer": "80"
                },
                {
                    "question": "30 + 5",
                    "answer": "35"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 6",
                    "answer": "69"
                },
                {
                    "question": "27 + 2",
                    "answer": "29"
                },
                {
                    "question": "65 + 2",
                    "answer": "67"
                },
                {
                    "question": "28 + 2",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "70 + 3",
                    "answer": "73"
                },
                {
                    "question": "69 + 8",
                    "answer": "77"
                },
                {
                    "question": "74 + 9",
                    "answer": "83"
                },
                {
                    "question": "36 + 6",
                    "answer": "42"
                },
                {
                    "question": "72 + 6",
                    "answer": "78"
                },
                {
                    "question": "66 + 7",
                    "answer": "73"
                },
                {
                    "question": "60 + 3",
                    "answer": "63"
                },
                {
                    "question": "36 + 7",
                    "answer": "43"
                },
                {
                    "question": "70 + 3",
                    "answer": "73"
                },
                {
                    "question": "28 + 6",
                    "answer": "34"
                },
                {
                    "question": "58 + 7",
                    "answer": "65"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 6",
                    "answer": "41"
                },
                {
                    "question": "13 + 3",
                    "answer": "16"
                },
                {
                    "question": "16 + 3",
                    "answer": "19"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 3",
                    "answer": "57"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 + 3",
                    "answer": "18"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25 + 2",
                    "answer": "27"
                },
                {
                    "question": "58 + 8",
                    "answer": "66"
                },
                {
                    "question": "80 + 9",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "98 + 3",
                    "answer": "101"
                },
                {
                    "question": "45 + 7",
                    "answer": "52"
                },
                {
                    "question": "68 + 7",
                    "answer": "75"
                },
                {
                    "question": "73 + 7",
                    "answer": "80"
                },
                {
                    "question": "21 + 7",
                    "answer": "28"
                },
                {
                    "question": "48 + 7",
                    "answer": "55"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 6",
                    "answer": "41"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 6",
                    "answer": "60"
                },
                {
                    "question": "51 + 9",
                    "answer": "60"
                },
                {
                    "question": "72 + ",
                    "answer": "78"
                },
                {
                    "question": "39 + 5",
                    "answer": "44"
                },
                {
                    "question": "68 + 9",
                    "answer": "77"
                },
                {
                    "question": "48 + 5",
                    "answer": "53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 9",
                    "answer": "33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "86 + 3",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "52 + 4",
                    "answer": "56"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 4",
                    "answer": "67"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 7",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 6",
                    "answer": "84"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 + 7",
                    "answer": "22"
                },
                {
                    "question": "51 + 9",
                    "answer": "60"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 3",
                    "answer": "86"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 2",
                    "answer": "37"
                },
                {
                    "question": "92 + 2",
                    "answer": "94"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 7",
                    "answer": "42"
                },
                {
                    "question": "97 + 8",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "16 + 6",
                    "answer": "22"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25 + 8",
                    "answer": "33"
                },
                {
                    "question": "34 + 9",
                    "answer": "43"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 + 9",
                    "answer": "24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "38 + 9",
                    "answer": "47"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 4",
                    "answer": "58"
                },
                {
                    "question": "81 + 3",
                    "answer": "84"
                },
                {
                    "question": "87 + 2",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 2",
                    "answer": "85"
                },
                {
                    "question": "43 + 5",
                    "answer": "48"
                },
                {
                    "question": "48 + 5",
                    "answer": "53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "91 + 2",
                    "answer": "93"
                },
                {
                    "question": "49 + 9",
                    "answer": "58"
                },
                {
                    "question": "22 + 9",
                    "answer": "31"
                },
                {
                    "question": "81 + 9",
                    "answer": "90"
                },
                {
                    "question": "58 + 5",
                    "answer": "63"
                },
                {
                    "question": "82 + 7",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "21 + 9",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "90 + 8",
                    "answer": "98"
                },
                {
                    "question": "46 + 2",
                    "answer": "48"
                },
                {
                    "question": "53 + 3",
                    "answer": "56"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 2",
                    "answer": "25"
                },
                {
                    "question": "86 + 2",
                    "answer": "88"
                },
                {
                    "question": "59 + 2",
                    "answer": "61"
                },
                {
                    "question": "29 + 5",
                    "answer": "34"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 3",
                    "answer": "86"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 + 7",
                    "answer": "57"
                },
                {
                    "question": "93 + 2",
                    "answer": "95"
                },
                {
                    "question": "94 + 8",
                    "answer": "102"
                },
                {
                    "question": "84 + 2",
                    "answer": "86"
                },
                {
                    "question": "91 + 9",
                    "answer": "100"
                },
                {
                    "question": "45 + 8",
                    "answer": "53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "76 + 2",
                    "answer": "78"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "title": "Math training 2",
            "pack": "Addition",
            "problems": [
                {
                    "question": "64 + 60",
                    "answer": "124"
                },
                {
                    "question": "19 + 34",
                    "answer": "53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "57 + 79",
                    "answer": "136"
                },
                {
                    "question": "46 + 42",
                    "answer": "88"
                },
                {
                    "question": "99 + 80",
                    "answer": "179"
                },
                {
                    "question": "32 + 33",
                    "answer": "65"
                },
                {
                    "question": "88 + 14",
                    "answer": "102"
                },
                {
                    "question": "76 + 51",
                    "answer": "127"
                },
                {
                    "question": "53 + 99",
                    "answer": "152"
                },
                {
                    "question": "44 + 54",
                    "answer": "98"
                },
                {
                    "question": "94 + 28",
                    "answer": "122"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 58",
                    "answer": "82"
                },
                {
                    "question": "89 + 54",
                    "answer": "143"
                },
                {
                    "question": "81 + 16",
                    "answer": "97"
                },
                {
                    "question": "40 + 92",
                    "answer": "132"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 17",
                    "answer": "100"
                },
                {
                    "question": "69 + 51",
                    "answer": "120"
                },
                {
                    "question": "99 + 14",
                    "answer": "113"
                },
                {
                    "question": "89 + 15",
                    "answer": "104"
                },
                {
                    "question": "61 + 83",
                    "answer": "144"
                },
                {
                    "question": "47 + 80",
                    "answer": "127"
                },
                {
                    "question": "13 + 30",
                    "answer": "43"
                },
                {
                    "question": "43 + 62",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "14 + 99",
                    "answer": "113"
                },
                {
                    "question": "70 + 19",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "64 + 75",
                    "answer": "139"
                },
                {
                    "question": "29 + 24",
                    "answer": "53"
                },
                {
                    "question": "45 + 18",
                    "answer": "63"
                },
                {
                    "question": "13 + 84",
                    "answer": "97"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 61",
                    "answer": "144"
                },
                {
                    "question": "90 + 51",
                    "answer": "141"
                },
                {
                    "question": "62 + 15",
                    "answer": "77"
                },
                {
                    "question": "48 + 22",
                    "answer": "70"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 81",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "56 + 72",
                    "answer": "128"
                },
                {
                    "question": "92 + 21",
                    "answer": "113"
                },
                {
                    "question": "44 + 74",
                    "answer": "118"
                },
                {
                    "question": "17 + 81",
                    "answer": "98"
                },
                {
                    "question": "37 + 80",
                    "answer": "117"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 70",
                    "answer": "124"
                },
                {
                    "question": "95 + 66",
                    "answer": "161"
                },
                {
                    "question": "90 + 65",
                    "answer": "155"
                },
                {
                    "question": "32 + 39",
                    "answer": "71"
                },
                {
                    "question": "22 + 63",
                    "answer": "85"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 81",
                    "answer": "104"
                },
                {
                    "question": "43 + 87",
                    "answer": "130"
                },
                {
                    "question": "42 + 18",
                    "answer": "60"
                },
                {
                    "question": "90 + 57",
                    "answer": "147"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 61",
                    "answer": "96"
                },
                {
                    "question": "99 + 52",
                    "answer": "151"
                },
                {
                    "question": "80 + 85",
                    "answer": "165"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 17",
                    "answer": "41"
                },
                {
                    "question": "17 + 97",
                    "answer": "114"
                },
                {
                    "question": "72 + 74",
                    "answer": "146"
                },
                {
                    "question": "58 + 88",
                    "answer": "146"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 + 57",
                    "answer": "107"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 40",
                    "answer": "118"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 26",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "62 + 26",
                    "answer": "88"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 + 76",
                    "answer": "126"
                },
                {
                    "question": "43 + 58",
                    "answer": "101"
                },
                {
                    "question": "57 + 54",
                    "answer": "111"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 72",
                    "answer": "135"
                },
                {
                    "question": "56 + 21",
                    "answer": "77"
                },
                {
                    "question": "28 + 45",
                    "answer": "73"
                },
                {
                    "question": "33 + 88",
                    "answer": "121"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 51",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "21 + 60",
                    "answer": "81"
                },
                {
                    "question": "74 + 63",
                    "answer": "137"
                },
                {
                    "question": "98 + 87",
                    "answer": "185"
                },
                {
                    "question": "59 + 16",
                    "answer": "75"
                },
                {
                    "question": "44 + 65",
                    "answer": "109"
                },
                {
                    "question": "29 + 50",
                    "answer": "79"
                },
                {
                    "question": "43 + 28",
                    "answer": "71"
                },
                {
                    "question": "95 + 80",
                    "answer": "175"
                },
                {
                    "question": "96 + 96",
                    "answer": "192"
                },
                {
                    "question": "28 + 58",
                    "answer": "86"
                },
                {
                    "question": "98 + 54",
                    "answer": "152"
                },
                {
                    "question": "64 + 31",
                    "answer": "95"
                },
                {
                    "question": "18 + 86",
                    "answer": "104"
                },
                {
                    "question": "80 + 42",
                    "answer": "122"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 29",
                    "answer": "112"
                },
                {
                    "question": "77 + 65",
                    "answer": "142"
                },
                {
                    "question": "81 + 55",
                    "answer": "136"
                },
                {
                    "question": "95 + 66",
                    "answer": "161"
                },
                {
                    "question": "71 + 46",
                    "answer": "117"
                },
                {
                    "question": "77 + 73",
                    "answer": "150"
                },
                {
                    "question": "19 + 47",
                    "answer": "66"
                },
                {
                    "question": "98 + 29",
                    "answer": "127"
                },
                {
                    "question": "13 + 58",
                    "answer": "71"
                },
                {
                    "question": "33 + 71",
                    "answer": "104"
                },
                {
                    "question": "96 + 27",
                    "answer": "123"
                },
                {
                    "question": "55 + 93",
                    "answer": "148"
                },
                {
                    "question": "70 + 56",
                    "answer": "126"
                },
                {
                    "question": "17 + 19",
                    "answer": "36"
                },
                {
                    "question": "78 + 67",
                    "answer": "145"
                },
                {
                    "question": "18 + 90",
                    "answer": "108"
                },
                {
                    "question": "38 + 54",
                    "answer": "92"
                },
                {
                    "question": "21 + 67",
                    "answer": "88"
                },
                {
                    "question": "97 + 57",
                    "answer": "154"
                },
                {
                    "question": "88 + 50",
                    "answer": "138"
                },
                {
                    "question": "87 + 29",
                    "answer": "116"
                },
                {
                    "question": "21 + 93",
                    "answer": "114"
                },
                {
                    "question": "93 + 51",
                    "answer": "144"
                },
                {
                    "question": "73 + 61",
                    "answer": "134"
                },
                {
                    "question": "64 + 80",
                    "answer": "144"
                },
                {
                    "question": "19 + 26",
                    "answer": "45"
                },
                {
                    "question": "13 + 18",
                    "answer": "31"
                },
                {
                    "question": "64 + 50",
                    "answer": "114"
                },
                {
                    "question": "45 + 86",
                    "answer": "131"
                },
                {
                    "question": "55 + 89",
                    "answer": "144"
                },
                {
                    "question": "29 + 37",
                    "answer": "66"
                },
                {
                    "question": "44 + 44",
                    "answer": "88"
                },
                {
                    "question": "83 + 56",
                    "answer": "139"
                },
                {
                    "question": "66 + 30",
                    "answer": "96"
                },
                {
                    "question": "16 + 98",
                    "answer": "114"
                },
                {
                    "question": "16 + 14",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "96 + 42",
                    "answer": "138"
                },
                {
                    "question": "32 + 16",
                    "answer": "48"
                },
                {
                    "question": "24 + 26",
                    "answer": "50"
                },
                {
                    "question": "55 + 25",
                    "answer": "80"
                },
                {
                    "question": "34 + 71",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "53 + 62",
                    "answer": "115"
                },
                {
                    "question": "41 + 62",
                    "answer": "103"
                },
                {
                    "question": "88 + 54",
                    "answer": "142"
                },
                {
                    "question": "15 + 74",
                    "answer": "89"
                },
                {
                    "question": "40 + 19",
                    "answer": "59"
                },
                {
                    "question": "62 + 65",
                    "answer": "127"
                },
                {
                    "question": "26 + 79",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "52 + 28",
                    "answer": "80"
                },
                {
                    "question": "68 + 46",
                    "answer": "114"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 89",
                    "answer": "124"
                },
                {
                    "question": "62 + 98",
                    "answer": "160"
                },
                {
                    "question": "70 + 26",
                    "answer": "96"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 31",
                    "answer": "85"
                },
                {
                    "question": "92 + 89",
                    "answer": "181"
                },
                {
                    "question": "23 + 17",
                    "answer": "40"
                },
                {
                    "question": "73 + 54",
                    "answer": "127"
                },
                {
                    "question": "36 + 70",
                    "answer": "106"
                },
                {
                    "question": "22 + 62",
                    "answer": "84"
                },
                {
                    "question": "93 + 68",
                    "answer": "161"
                },
                {
                    "question": "32 + 20",
                    "answer": "52"
                },
                {
                    "question": "63 + 72",
                    "answer": "135"
                },
                {
                    "question": "88 + 67",
                    "answer": "155"
                },
                {
                    "question": "47 + 48",
                    "answer": "95"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 66",
                    "answer": "101"
                },
                {
                    "question": "54 + 54",
                    "answer": "108"
                },
                {
                    "question": "35 + 29",
                    "answer": "64"
                },
                {
                    "question": "86 + 64",
                    "answer": "150"
                },
                {
                    "question": "75 + 68",
                    "answer": "143"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "20",
            "title": "Subtraction 1",
            "pack": "Subtraction",
            "problems": [
                {
                    "question": "12 - 3",
                    "answer": "9"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "21",
            "title": "Subtraction 2",
            "pack": "Subtraction",
            "problems": [
                {
                    "question": "25 - 8",
                    "answer": "17"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}